Antony TRORY

07956 565661 | antony.trory@sky.com

TRADING TRANSACTION COST ANALYST

An accomplished Trading Transaction Cost Analyst with considerable experience across investment management, trading oversight and regulatory compliance. Significant governance and stakeholder engagement experience as a committee member and secretary, contributing to trade oversight, compliance with FCA commission unbundling rules, and industry working groups on costs and charges. Delivered measurable results by designing Power BI dashboards and Excel-based solutions that enhanced TCA data analysis, implementing systems to track dilution levies and regulatory client reporting and optimising processes to reduce settlement risk and increase transparency.

SKILLS

Investment Management | Compliance | Data Analysis | Reporting | Stakeholder Engagement | Process Improvement | PowerBI

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TRANSACTION COST ANALYST (TCA)

November 2018 to October 2024

Columbia Threadneedle Investments / Bank of Montreal GAM EMEA

Designed and delivered routine and ad-hoc TCA related reporting (using Power BI) for Traders, Regional Heads of Trading, Trade Oversight Advisory Group and Clients.

 Member of the Trade Oversight Advisory Group (working group of the Investment Management Committee). TCA ANALYST March 2018 to November 2021

Bank of Montreal GAM EMEA

Effectively managed TCA across Equity, Fixed Income, FX and ETD.

- Designed and delivered TCA reporting for Dealers, Head of Dealing and the Commission and TCA Committee.
- Secretary and member of the Commission and TCA Committee.

SENIOR DEALING SUPPORT ANALYST

January 2005 - March 2018

Bank of Montreal GAM EMEA

Delivered oversight of outsourced back and middle office functions, helping to resolve trade settlement and confirmation queries.

- · Member of the IA Costs and Charges Working Group.
- Implemented, managed and evolved the RECAP system and internal procedures to manage the FCA commission unbundling rule, produced CSA statements and half-yearly regulatory client reporting.
- Designed and implemented reporting solution to monitor, track and set dilution levies for pooled funds.
- Collaborated extensively with the external Equity TCA system provider to deliver appropriately benchmarked analysis.
- Created and implemented an Excel solution to summarise and enable granular analysis of Equity TCA data.
- Managed the Dealing Desk policies and procedures including Order Execution Policy, Order Aggregation and Allocation Policy and Research Commissions.
- Represented the Dealing function for the implementation of thinkFolio (OMS).

EARLIER CAREER SUMMARY

MANAGEMENT INFORMATION ANALYST, Folgate Risk Solutions

MANAGEMENT INFORMATION OFFICER, Isis Asset Management

MANAGEMENT INFORMATION ANALYST, KWELM Management Services Ltd

EDUCATION

A Level in Economics - Emerson Park School

GCSE's including Maths (B), English Language (B), English Literature (B) and Biology (C) - Emerson Park School